Are.  There may be some upside here.
Well, along with this, Sir, the
numbers of ICICI LBRD have also come.
You will see that their profits have also fallen by 79% in the year.  However,
total income has grown by around 12%.  Net
premium earned has also increased by around 13%.  The
combined ratio has also improved.
But
how do you see the impact of the 9% drop in profits on the charts?
Today?
Look, this may have a short term reaction.
Rest I don't think it will
fall more, it will come down more, I am not able to see that
because overall
this space is positive.  And if by chance
some virus or something comes into the world
again, you will see the entire counter will
run away.  So I am not able to see much effect.
You will be advised to buy on deep.  If it
comes down then there is a buying opportunity for you
from 17780 to 1750 maximum
in the short term, if it comes down then it will become a
buying opportunity for you on a healthy correction.
Oh okay.  OK, that's perfect.  This will be about ICICI Ltd.
good its